http request:
TCP connection to server opened by browser
If secure, TLS certificates are issued to prevent eavesdropping and stealing data.

Browser sends http message with url (get, post, etc)

Server performs requested actions, and sends response with status message with data
Once response is received, tcp connection is closed
http is stateless

http/2 allows multiplexing transactions take place over same tcp at same time
Allows server to push data to browser at same time
Improves performance
Reduce lag

———————————————————————————

 Why we chose to go with index.html
How url works and why index or default.html is useful

———————————————————————————
http methods
Show demonstrations on the browser using inspect and network

Show header anatomy
e.g.
GET - by client (browser)
Response from server
